<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Activity Challenge</string>
    <string name="button_one">Text one</string>
    <string name="button_two">Text two</string>
    <string name="button_three">Text three</string>

<!--    second activity-->

    <string name="text_one"><b>Coding</b>\n\nCoding is basically the computer language used to develop apps, websites, and software. Without it, we’d have none of the most popular technology we\’ve come to rely on such as Facebook, our smartphones, the browser we choose to view our favorite blogs, or even the blogs themselves. It all runs on code.\n
    To put it very simply, the code is what tells your computer what to do. Sports or athletic games typically performed in the open, including physical exertion, are referred to as outdoor games. All across the world, people enjoy playing outdoor games and sports since they are fun and beneficial for physical fitness. But these outdoor games for kids no longer hold as much significance in light of the rising popularity of video games, online games, and gaming devices.\nTo put it very simply, the code is what tells your computer what to do.To go a bit deeper, computers don’t understand words. They only understand the concepts of on and off. The capabilities of a computer are guided by on and off switches, or transistors. Binary code represents these on and off transistors as the digits 1 and 0. An infinite number of combinations of these codes make your computer work. In order to make binary code manageable, computer programming languages were formed. These languages each serve different purposes, but they all allow programmers to translate important commands into binary code.Sports or athletic games typically performed in the open, including physical exertion, are referred to as outdoor games. All across the world, people enjoy playing outdoor games and sports since they are fun and beneficial for physical fitness. But these outdoor games for kids no longer hold as much significance in light of the rising popularity of video games, online games, and gaming devices.\nTo put it very simply, the code is what tells your computer what to do.</string>
    <string name="text_two"><b>Gaming</b>\n\nSports or athletic games typically performed in the open, including physical exertion, are referred to as outdoor games. All across the world, people enjoy playing outdoor games and sports since they are fun and beneficial for physical fitness. But these outdoor games for kids no longer hold as much significance in light of the rising popularity of video games, online games, and gaming devices.Sports or athletic games typically performed in the open, including physical exertion, are referred to as outdoor games. All across the world, people enjoy playing outdoor games and sports since they are fun and beneficial for physical fitness. But these outdoor games for kids no longer hold as much significance in light of the rising popularity of video games, online games, and gaming devices.\nTo put it very simply, the code is what tells your computer what to do.\nTo put it very simply, the code is what tells your computer what to do. To go a bit deeper, computers don’t understand words. They only understand the concepts of on and off. The capabilities of a computer are guided by on and off switches, or transistors.Sports or athletic games typically performed in the open, including physical exertion, are referred to as outdoor games. All across the world, people enjoy playing outdoor games and sports since they are fun and beneficial for physical fitness. But these outdoor games for kids no longer hold as much significance in light of the rising popularity of video games, online games, and gaming devices.\nTo put it very simply, the code is what tells your computer what to do.</string>
    <string name="text_three"><b>Entertainment</b>\n\nEntertainment is a form of activity that holds the attention and interest of an audience or gives pleasure and delight. It can be an idea or a task, but is more likely to be one of the activities or events that have developed over thousands of years specifically for the purpose of keeping an audience\'s attention.\nTo put it very simply, the code is what tells your computer what to do. To go a bit deeper, computers don’t understand words. They only understand the concepts of on and off. The capabilities of a computer are guided by on and off switches, or transistors.Sports or athletic games typically performed in the open, including physical exertion, are referred to as outdoor games. All across the world, people enjoy playing outdoor games and sports since they are fun and beneficial for physical fitness. Sports or athletic games typically performed in the open, including physical exertion, are referred to as outdoor games. All across the world, people enjoy playing outdoor games and sports since they are fun and beneficial for physical fitness. But these outdoor games for kids no longer hold as much significance in light of the rising popularity of video games, online games, and gaming devices.\nTo put it very simply, the code is what tells your computer what to do.But these outdoor games for kids no longer hold as much significance in light of the rising popularity of video games, online games, and gaming devices.\nTo put it very simply, the code is what tells your computer what to do.</string>
</resources>